It's coming in from here.
Yes, sir.
We've confirmed that...
Mariko apparently...
We know that she likes fortune tellers.
That's right.
Correct.
Wasn't it mentioned that she was like someone's daughter?
that
Daughter.
Spoiler alert.
It's online.
That's right.
So they're all related, right?
So we're all related by blood.
A big family.
Let's resume with full energy, everyone, please.
Here we go.
Hello.
Hello again.
Thank you very much.
And that's why we're doing a live broadcast.
If you're watching the live broadcast, you know...
Mariko is shining.
She's shining like gold!
Just in case you haven't noticed, Mariko has turned gold this week.
Mariko the Gold, that's what they're calling me this week.
That's a devil name.
It's so cool!
I'm sorry it took so long.
It's like a gang of thieves.
Like they leave letters with diamonds and stuff.
Cool.
Maricothe Gold.
Maricoza Gold did the job.
I did my job.
So that's a little bit.
We're going to go ahead with the recording again, so...
I'm looking forward to working with you.
You scared me. What is it?
What is it?
You're holding a muscle.
He's been doing that all week, as usual.
You scared me.
You scared the shit out of me, too.
I'm the one who's surprised.
Week in, week out.
I get all kinds of letters.
You know, genres...
All kinds of things.
For example, we meet at Rasha's.
I've been on various trips and so on.
This week, there are many photos of food, so let's take a look at some of them.
Let's see, first of all...
First of all, we received this from Mr. 119 from Konan-ku, Yokohama City, who has been talking about it a lot lately.
Thank you very much.
Master Ebichu, Mr. Sarpon, good evening!
The other day, the tower kata-yakisoba became a topic of conversation.
They serve kata-yakisoba like this.
It's a little bit like making it taller.
I also have a restaurant near Tateuchi Station called Benihana.
I often go to Benihana. It's right next to the station.
It's a restaurant with a reputation for good food, and I had kata yakisoba there.
It's been a while since I've had kenyakisoba, but I thought a picture of kenyakisoba would be enough.
Almost.
Looks delicious!
It looks so delicious!
We probably started talking about kata yakisoba...
Then we talked about cat's tongue.
and then we talked about small baskets.
I'm sure.
That's why the one-sided fried noodles is a fateful encounter.
I've never been attacked by him. I've been accused of having a cat's tongue.
I'm totally fine with hot food.
Mariko is invincible... she can handle spicy food and even bugs.
but she doesn't eat it... but she got it... she grabbed it...
Well, hard fried noodles...
For those who have cat's tongue...
It's one of the most difficult enemies for those with cat's tongue.
Yes, the ones with starchy sauce...
It doesn't look so hot at a glance.
That's right.
It's good, but when you try to eat it
When you try to eat it, it gets all smoky...
Smoke
It's so bright.
I haven't had it in a while.
It's good.
When they serve kata-yakisoba, I usually stay for 10 minutes.
huh?
You're watching.
Heh.
That's pretty good.
Someone tells me it's time to go.
Like, "Thank you very much.
Like this, right? Like the basket of dumplings?
Yes, what was it? Some kind of meat? Pork belly stew?
The one you recommended was also covered with sauce.
And he just kept looking at it.
That's what we call "looking". "Looking" is written "seeing".
I see. So you were watching.
If Mariko were to eat soba, she'd have to eat mustard too.
I wonder if she has any weaknesses... or any food she doesn't like. Nothing you can't eat? No!
Damn!
Me neither.
No?
Yes!
We're fucked.
What else?
Yes, I have.
I mean, you don't really like...
Broccoli, for example.
I can eat cucumbers for religious reasons.
I always say it's for religious reasons.
There is a religion that people don't know about.
It's kind of hard to get into.
Religious reasons...
It depends on the person.
That's right.
That's how I always try to escape.
You're good at it.
You're good at running away... if that's the way you run away...
This is a travel photo.
Suginami, Tokyo... a night commuter... a pirate.
He took a highway bus from Shinjuku to Kanazawa via Tobita Takayama.
He went to Kanazawa via Tobita-Takayama.
I miss highway buses.
Like this.
From Shinjuku
From Bussta.
Bussta.
Like a gas station.
Like a gas station. Buster! What's a Busstar? Like a gas station, like a gas station.
Buster.
Buster, get in here.
So, um...
When I was young, I used to take the express bus when I wanted to go somewhere because it was cheaper.
But back then, the environment was...
The environment wasn't comfortable like it is now.
It was very hard.
I felt like my ass was really hot.
You can't really adjust the heating.
It was like "atch atch atch".
I heard it's comfortable now.
You can see all kinds of things.
And they put up these shutters.
It's easy to sleep with it shielded from the sun.
I think it's getting better now.
Also, the performance of the buses has improved.
Suspension and so on.
It's not shaking.
I thought it might be more comfortable.
First of all, this...
First of all, this.
There's a service area on the Chuo Expressway called Kuruma Soba.
I use it more often than this place.
The raw egg is good.
You can see the whole lake.
You can see the entire lake from the Suwako Service Area on the Chuo Expressway.
I was probably born around here.
Wow!
It's on the shore of Suwa Lake.
Do you have a house?
There was a hospital here back then.
I see.
I wasn't born at home.
I'm sorry, I wasn't born at home.
I was born at home... a long time ago.
I'm sorry, it's a hospital.
I've never seen it in person.
I've never seen anyone born at home.
It's rare.
I was wrong.
I miss the birdhouse.
This is what a birdhouse looks like now.
When it's really cold, it freezes over.
Wow.
Even though it's this big.
Wow, that's amazing!
When it was small.
There were people skating on it when I was little.
Amazing!
Natural ice
Natural ice.
And of course...
Speaking of Hita Takayama
Shirakawa-go
Shirakawa-go is this kind of Gassho
It's like a breakup.
Not much snow this year, huh?
It sure feels like there's not much.
Not much?
Definitely less, because it's already a heavy snowfall area.
I see.
These so-called buildings are nice.
It's like a Japanese folk tale.
There are Zashiki Warashi, you know.
Zashiki Warashi.
And finally we went to Kanazawa.
Have you ever been to Kanazawa station?
Yes, I have.
It's really cool.
It's amazing.
It's a structure.
I was surprised when I saw it for the first time.
It looks like this.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
And, uh...
This is a bit of a train story.
There's a bullet train called "Doctor Yellow".
Yes?
You know it?
Yes, I've heard of it.
What's it all about?
It's not yellow in color. It's yellow in color.
The color is yellow.
Okay, I think I may have beaten Mariko for the first time today.
Basically, they're running around checking the tracks and stuff.
Amazing!
Shinkansen inspection cars are not allowed to be ridden by ordinary cars.
But while running on the track, they check if the track is bent or not.
or if there are any bumps on the track
But I can't tell you when and where they are coming.
But it's hard to tell when and where they'll be coming.
The general public is not informed at all
Suddenly, when I'm waiting at Shin-Yokohama station
I'm waiting at Shin-Yokohama station or something, and the kids are making a big fuss
They're saying things like...
What's going on?
It's the doctor.
I'm sure it's just an inspection car, but the bullet train's a little short, so I figured the kids would stop at the other end and... Oh, no... That Doctor Yellow Beatrice, Tama City, Tokyo...
Thank you very much.
Like this.
It's a kind of a candid shot, isn't it?
Maybe he just happened to pass by.
I've only seen it once or twice.
I think it was a 4-car train.
That's right.
It's filled with various measuring instruments.
Doctor Yellow is very popular.
That's right.
The doctor of bullet trains.
Yes, Doctor Yellow.
And a quote...
Let's talk about quotes...
You know, of course...
Suzuki is a manufacturer of motorcycles and cars.
The founder of the company is...
His name is Mr. Suzuki, right?
His name is Michio Suzuki.
He's like this.
But the thing is...
He was born in the 20th year of Meiji Era.
He was born in the 20th year of Meiji era.
The 20th year of the Meiji era.
That's amazing.
It's been around for such a long time.
Because, as I recall, the Meiji period lasted until 40 or so years ago.
After that, there was the Taisho period, and then the Showa period.
That's right.
He probably worked until he was about 90 years old.
That's amazing.
In 1982.
Founder of Suzuki of the World
Michio Suzuki, founder of World Suzuki Co.
It's straightforward, after all.
If it's something the customer wants
Do whatever you have to do to answer them.
If you work hard, you can do it.
Wow!
That's amazing.
If today's young people heard this, they might say it's impossible.
Impossible!
It's really impossible!
Like, "Mr. Michio, it's impossible!
I can't do it... Mr. Michio can't do it.
I heard the employees are talking to the founder like he's their friend.
It's true... he turned 95 last year.
That's amazing.
I see.
Suzuki is famous for cars, of course, but also for motorcycles.
They're also famous for motorcycles, and I was looking into Suzuki motorcycles for a while.
I was researching a lot about Suzuki bikes for a while, and there are a lot of bikes that have such nice equipment for such a low price range.
It's the same with cars.
Really?
Well, I've never owned a Suzuki car.
I've never owned a Suzuki car, but for work, I've rented cars at random.
Of course, there are Nissan, Honda, Toyota, and so on.
Of course, there are Nissan, Honda, Toyota, and so on, but...
But suddenly a Suzuki car comes along.
It's amazing!
What? It's got a dash!
I thought, "This is a very cost-effective car.
There's a car called Swift.
I thought it was a great car.
From the wonderful words of Mr. Michio
If someone from Suzuki shows it to me, I'll give one to them.
I'm looking forward to seeing a self-designed car, too.
I'd rather have a manual Swift R.
I'm a self-drive driver.
I don't have a license.
You can get it at home.
Don't people around here get licenses?
I'd like to, but my mom says I don't need one.
I'd rather not have it.
If I lived in Tokyo, I wouldn't have the chance to drive.
That's very true, but...
I'm sure it'll come in handy when there's something you can't transport with this thing.
I'd like you to get a driver's license or something... I'd like you to taste the hardships of the driving school that we're going through.
I don't want to do it again.
I don't want to do it again I don't want to go to a driving school ever again.
I can only take about two classes a day.
Unlike a training camp, you can't take it all at once.
So you have to make an appointment every morning and go early in the morning.
When we were there, all the people at the driving school were scary, so we had to go early in the morning.
like a punch palm sitting next to you.
Like, "Hey, you're not looking in the rearview mirror.
They were filming all the time in the early morning.
I wonder how long it would take to film at a normal place like that.
I don't know.
I don't know, until the last graduation.
I don't know, six months, three months?
Three months? No, maybe three months.
I took it when I was graduating from high school.
So maybe two months.
I started to lead a very regular life, day after day.
Isn't that a good thing?
I used to wake up as much as I could when I thought it was okay to laugh.
It's pretty late.
Who? I was just thinking.
Oh, man, I gotta go to Teacher Sushi.
He got mad at me and came home.
I think it was a good social lesson.
Yes, it was.
It taught me that the world isn't so easy to live in.
Driving is dangerous.
That's right.
That's about right.
It's too harsh.
I know I just said that, but...
I'm also grateful for the perm.
That's right.
I had a female instructor like that.
She was very strict.
Surprisingly, so was I.
So was Panchi.
But the woman, she seemed so kind.
She just sat there and didn't say anything.
She didn't say anything, so I asked her what was wrong.
She was like, "Not at all.
That's exactly what I was saying.
It's not like anything happened to me.
It's just that the air in the car...
There were only two people in the car.
That's true, isn't it?
There it is.
No, no, no.
You know, in the end, Ebituaries...
You know, the acquisition rate is usually very low.
Miele.
About as much as I want.
Certainly.
Not much use in Tokyo.
I don't know if there's much use for it in Tokyo.
For now.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well, well...
Well, well, well...
So... we're about to have the "Devil's Gate" in Odate...
Yesterday or the day before...
I've been thinking about what we should do for BFF.
We've been discussing about it.
We haven't decided on the details yet.
I can't tell you about it.
But I heard that you and I are going to do something.
Oh, well...
I don't know...
Are you going to say something?
No, no, no, no.
It's been a while since I sang.
It's like...
What's this?
It sounds like an apostle.
The apostles are coming!
I hope you're looking forward to it!
And as for the tickets, they're on sale now!
Please buy them!
Please do!
Please come!
Why now?
Don't be cold.
That's right. Suddenly.
From Mariko's side too.
I'm sorry. From Mariko the Gold's side too.
Mr. Nagayama... we'd like to ask a favor from Mariko's side as well.
If you could just say so...
Of course everyone will come.
We'll open the schedule.
We're waiting for you.
I'm waiting for you...
I went blonde.
I went blonde because I went crazy.
I'm not kidding... you should ask him where he went to middle school.
Where did he go to middle school?
Which middle school?
You're getting more powerful, that's for sure!
I'll be looking forward to seeing you again.
That's all for now.
Next week, the live broadcast will be moved up one hour to 7:00 p.m.
I hope to see you all again at 7:00 p.m., and I hope to see you all there.
I hope to see you all again at 7:00 p.m., and I hope to see you all again in good health.
Well, we're off now.
Thank you very much.
See you next week at 7:00 p.m.
I'll see you next week at 7:00 p.m.
Thank you very much.
See you next week.
7:00 p.m.